[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Suzanne Kelly, where do we even start with this?", "question_tokens": ["Suzanne", "Kelly", ",", "where", "do", "we", "even", "start", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Suzanne Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Suzanne"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Barbara Starr, can you clear up what we should make of this?", "question_tokens": ["Barbara", "Starr", ",", "can", "you", "clear", "up", "what", "we", "should", "make", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I think I'm going to vote with Suzanne.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "vote", "with", "Suzanne", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara Starr"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "You might think it's Hollywood but it's -- you know, it's really -- the circles of power in Washington, what on earth has been going on?", "question_tokens": ["You", "might", "think", "it", "'s", "Hollywood", "but", "it", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "--", "the", "circles", "of", "power", "in", "Washington", ",", "what", "on", "earth", "has", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "And what is extraordinary about this.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "extraordinary", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How credible is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "credible", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Yes -- this is a -- this is a very fundamental problem.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--", "this", "is", "a", "--", "this", "is", "a", "very", "fundamental", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Would you have felt an obligation to inform the president or somebody senior in the White House if you got wind of this kind of scandal enveloping the boss of the CIA?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "felt", "an", "obligation", "to", "inform", "the", "president", "or", "somebody", "senior", "in", "the", "White", "House", "if", "you", "got", "wind", "of", "this", "kind", "of", "scandal", "enveloping", "the", "boss", "of", "the", "CIA", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, easy to say what I would have felt.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "easy", "to", "say", "what", "I", "would", "have", "felt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why would the FBI be involved in this anyway?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "the", "FBI", "be", "involved", "in", "this", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "The FBI is supposed to investigate predicated federal crimes.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "FBI", "is", "supposed", "to", "investigate", "predicated", "federal", "crimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Because he was kind of a bipartisan figure, Petraeus, lauded equally by Republicans and Democrats although you could argue that he was appointed to the CIA director's job by the president and therefore the president stood most to lose, would you think?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "he", "was", "kind", "of", "a", "bipartisan", "figure", ",", "Petraeus", ",", "lauded", "equally", "by", "Republicans", "and", "Democrats", "although", "you", "could", "argue", "that", "he", "was", "appointed", "to", "the", "CIA", "director", "'s", "job", "by", "the", "president", "and", "therefore", "the", "president", "stood", "most", "to", "lose", ",", "would", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJS", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, I don't think he stood to lose directly from this man's personal problem and personal tragedy, I might add.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "stood", "to", "lose", "directly", "from", "this", "man", "'s", "personal", "problem", "and", "personal", "tragedy", ",", "I", "might", "add", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "On everything we know right now, do you think Petraeus was right to resign?", "question_tokens": ["On", "everything", "we", "know", "right", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "Petraeus", "was", "right", "to", "resign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FDR"], "PERSON": ["Lucy Mercer"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Because he doesn't -- I mean, this has been analogized to other powerful men who have had mistresses from, you know, Lucy Mercer, FDR, to on and on and on.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "does", "n't", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "this", "has", "been", "analogized", "to", "other", "powerful", "men", "who", "have", "had", "mistresses", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Lucy", "Mercer", ",", "FDR", ",", "to", "on", "and", "on", "and", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "How has that led to a full-fledged investigation that brings down the CIA director?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "that", "led", "to", "a", "full-fledged", "investigation", "that", "brings", "down", "the", "CIA", "director", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "You couldn't have made this story up.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "n't", "have", "made", "this", "story", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "I mean it seems that the crucial twist in the tale which has emerged tonight is that this original FBI agent who was already friendly with Miss Kelley, he then gets taken off the case for inappropriate behavior, for supposedly sending shirtless pictures of himself to her, to the woman who has come to him to investigate, and because of that, he then feels disaffected and goes to a congressman, at which point the whole balloon goes up, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "seems", "that", "the", "crucial", "twist", "in", "the", "tale", "which", "has", "emerged", "tonight", "is", "that", "this", "original", "FBI", "agent", "who", "was", "already", "friendly", "with", "Miss", "Kelley", ",", "he", "then", "gets", "taken", "off", "the", "case", "for", "inappropriate", "behavior", ",", "for", "supposedly", "sending", "shirtless", "pictures", "of", "himself", "to", "her", ",", "to", "the", "woman", "who", "has", "come", "to", "him", "to", "investigate", ",", "and", "because", "of", "that", ",", "he", "then", "feels", "disaffected", "and", "goes", "to", "a", "congressman", ",", "at", "which", "point", "the", "whole", "balloon", "goes", "up", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "PERSON": ["Miss Kelley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 213, "question": "And where do shirtless pictures come into -- into the scene?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "do", "shirtless", "pictures", "come", "into", "--", "into", "the", "scene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "So from all you know, do you believe fundamentally they should have gone to the White House earlier?", "question_tokens": ["So", "from", "all", "you", "know", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "fundamentally", "they", "should", "have", "gone", "to", "the", "White", "House", "earlier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I think this is actually an open question even at the FBI, which is if we had life to live over, would we have done it differently.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "is", "actually", "an", "open", "question", "even", "at", "the", "FBI", ",", "which", "is", "if", "we", "had", "life", "to", "live", "over", ",", "would", "we", "have", "done", "it", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paula Broadwell"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Do you recognize the man that you've been reading about for the last 24 hours?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "recognize", "the", "man", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "reading", "about", "for", "the", "last", "24", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, in many ways, I do, because with this one exception of this incident that he had with Paula Broadwell, I think the fact that this was a guy that stood up when the facts became known, did the honorable thing and resigned.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "I", "do", ",", "because", "with", "this", "one", "exception", "of", "this", "incident", "that", "he", "had", "with", "Paula", "Broadwell", ",", "I", "think", "the", "fact", "that", "this", "was", "a", "guy", "that", "stood", "up", "when", "the", "facts", "became", "known", ",", "did", "the", "honorable", "thing", "and", "resigned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24 hours?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Should a general in his position, who has moved on to run the CIA, have to resign his post over an affair, which is really what this seems to have been about?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "a", "general", "in", "his", "position", ",", "who", "has", "moved", "on", "to", "run", "the", "CIA", ",", "have", "to", "resign", "his", "post", "over", "an", "affair", ",", "which", "is", "really", "what", "this", "seems", "to", "have", "been", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "My opinion, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "opinion", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Do you think he should have resigned?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "should", "have", "resigned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I think there's many other reasons Petraeus should have resigned besides who he's sleeping with that's not his wife.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "many", "other", "reasons", "Petraeus", "should", "have", "resigned", "besides", "who", "he", "'s", "sleeping", "with", "that", "'s", "not", "his", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Petraeus now has all his allies coming out to defend him, where Paula Broadwell is there yet again -- where are her protectors?", "question_tokens": ["Petraeus", "now", "has", "all", "his", "allies", "coming", "out", "to", "defend", "him", ",", "where", "Paula", "Broadwell", "is", "there", "yet", "again", "--", "where", "are", "her", "protectors", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Barbara is not a spokesperson for him, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["Barbara", "is", "not", "a", "spokesperson", "for", "him", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paula Broadwell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Yes, why not?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I think there are good points on both sides.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "are", "good", "points", "on", "both", "sides", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Why were you not a fan of General Petraeus?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "not", "a", "fan", "of", "General", "Petraeus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, the American media has come up with this narrative that he's the American hero who betrayed by the woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "American", "media", "has", "come", "up", "with", "this", "narrative", "that", "he", "'s", "the", "American", "hero", "who", "betrayed", "by", "the", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Were you surprised when Petraeus got the CIA job?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "when", "Petraeus", "got", "the", "CIA", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I was worried about it because he's created again -- the military crossing into the CIA is very dangerous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "worried", "about", "it", "because", "he", "'s", "created", "again", "--", "the", "military", "crossing", "into", "the", "CIA", "is", "very", "dangerous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "-- for him to resign?", "question_tokens": ["--", "for", "him", "to", "resign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "In England, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "England", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "That is quite dangerous, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "quite", "dangerous", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Very dangerous.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "dangerous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "On balance, are you pleased though that he won the election?", "question_tokens": ["On", "balance", ",", "are", "you", "pleased", "though", "that", "he", "won", "the", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I'm pleased he won the election.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pleased", "he", "won", "the", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Why did you want to make this series?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "want", "to", "make", "this", "series", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Boy.", "answer_tokens": ["Boy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]